(Sheldon:)Oh...
(Leonard:)Okay...
(Leonard:)Sheldon, hang tight.
(Leonard:)Hey, do you want me
to bring anything?
(Sheldon:)Oh, yes, please.
(Sheldon:)A pair of pants.
(Sheldon:)And my toothbrush.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, and my mail.
(Sheldon:)And a really good comeback
for Chicken Legs,
because "I know you are,
but what am I?"
(Sheldon:)was met with stony silence.
(Leonard:)I'll be there
as soon as I can.
(Penny:)Is he okay?
(Leonard:)Yeah, he's fine, he's
just a little rattled.
(Sheldon:)Oh...
Feel like driving
to Arizona with me?
(Penny:)I can't, I have
that job interview.
(Leonard:)Oh, right.
Besides,
(Penny:)I don't need six hours of
"Your hair is different.
"Why did you change your hair?
(Penny:)I'm holding my breath
until your hair grows back."
(Leonard:)All right, fine.
(Leonard:)Hey, can you
think of a reason
(Leonard:)I shouldn't invite
Amy to come with me?
Nope.
(Leonard:)Come on, you didn't even try.
(Raj:)Thanks for the lift.
(Howard:)What's wrong
with your car?
(Raj:)I'm having my windows untinted.
(Howard:)Why?
(Raj:)Got a hot girlfriend now.
(Raj:)I want the haters to know.
(Howard:)What are you talking about?
(Howard:)No one's paying
attention to you.
(Raj:)Wow.